# KATE PRASOLEK

## kate.prasolek@gmail.com | 07479929600 | London E1 4RS

kateprasolek.github.io/portfolio | behance.net/kateprasolek | linkedin.com/in/kateprasolek

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Reliable graphic designer with a friendly can-do attitude, experienced in both print and digital design. Self-learner of HTML, CSS and website design with good fundamentals of UI/UX best practices. Crafter with a natural eye for detail, layout and typography, currently learning motion design.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Adobe Photoshop	(4 years)	HTML, CSS	(2 years)	Dotdigital Emails	(2 years)
Adobe inDesign	(4 years)	Adobe XD	(1 year)	Litmus	(2 years)
Adobe Illustrator	(4 years)	Bootstrap	(2 years)	Git / Github	(2 years)
Adobe After Effects	(new)	Google Web Designer	(new)	Wordpress CMS	(5 years)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Graphic Digital Designer, London (Jan 2020 - present)

- Graphic digital designer at arteKatie develop the brand identity, product photography and retouching, design website banners and promotional marketing collateral. I achieved a 50% sales increase by consistent visuals and social media campaigns.
- Graphic designer at Naturewatch Foundation creating digital and print assets for campaigns.
- Work on web UI/UX design, landing pages, wireframes, prototypes and website mockups.

#### Graphic Designer at Wex Photo Video, London (Feb 2018 - Jan 2020)

- Create from brief to completion a wide range of marketing communications such as website banners, emails, gifs, brochures, leaflets, magazine's ads, large format prints and more.
- Work collaboratively with other teams and use feedback to produce final marketing creatives.
- Ensure compliance with brand guidelines and design consistency across all formats and channels.
- Manage multiple digital and print projects simultaneously adhering to meet deadlines.
- Supervise magazines' schedules, liaising with publishers and printers.
- Maintain templates and files, where I implemented a system that sped up the team's work-flow.

#### Freelance Graphic Designer, London (May 2016 - Feb 2018)

Create engaging logos, banners, brochures, leaflets and marketing materials for various clients.

#### Receptionist and Research Bank Worker at Poplar Harca, London (May 2015 - Nov 2017)

Reception duties and data administration. I put into practice a structured data entry process, that was easier for volunteers to understand and lower the number of mistakes.

#### Master Team Member at Paul UK (Jun 2013 - Feb 2015)

Supervising shift, organising displays and stock, handling orders, sales plans distribution, reporting and customer service. I achieved a 5% increase in sales by visually managing displays throughout the day.

#### Saleswoman at Polkomtel SA (Oct 2010 - Dec 2012)

Phone customer service duties, selling and extending contracts.

#### Shift Supervisor at Pizzeria laPrimera (May 2009 - Sep 2010)

Organising shifts, stock and deliveries, reporting.

#### INTERPERSONAL SOFT SKILLS

Attention to detail Reliability Time management Can-do attitude
Creativity Professionalism Organisation skills Ability to teamwork
Fast-learning Enthusiasm Prioritising Communications skills

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

2020 Adobe CC After Effects and XD Experience Design, UI design.

2018-19 Dotmailer/ Dotdigital, Adobe CC Illustrator.

2017 Adobe Dreamweaver, HTML emails, HTML5/ CSS3, Javascript, jQuery.

2016 Graphic Design, Layouts and Composition, Branding and Typography,

Adobe Creative Suite Photoshop and inDesign.

2008 Psychology, master degree, Silesian University.